♪A light shines on me♪
نور يضيء علي ♪
♪A leaf falls to the ground♪
ورقة تسقط على الأرض ♪
♪A person♪
شخص ♪
♪Living in another world♪
العيش في عالم آخر
♪A beating heart♪
قلب ينبض ♪
♪A gentle wind♪
♪ رياح لطيفة ♪
♪You bring me the light♪
أحضر لي النور
♪Falling in love in an instant♪
الوقوع في الحب في لحظة ♪
♪A story unfolds page by page♪
♪ قصة تتكشف صفحة بصفحة
♪A lonely heart is slowly warmed♪
قلب وحيد يسخن ببطء ♪
♪A star is twinkling♪
♪ نجمة متلألئة ♪
♪Destined to meet you♪
♪ متجه لمقابلتك ♪
♪You mean everything to me in reality or in my dreams♪
♪ أنت تعني لي كل شيء في الواقع أو في أحلامي ♪
=The Next Stop W= (Adapted from the TV series W – Two Worlds)
= المحطة التالية W = (مقتبس من المسلسل التلفزيوني W - عالمان)
=Episode 10=
= الحلقة 10 =
Let's end this.
دعونا ننهي هذا.
Who would have thought
من كان يظن
there were two people who stabbed me that day?
كان هناك شخصان طعناني ذلك اليوم؟
I never told anyone about this
لم أخبر أحدا عن هذا قط
due to the lack of proof.
بسبب عدم وجود دليل.
But my instinct tells me
لكن غريزتي تخبرني
the one who's trying everything to kill me
الشخص الذي يحاول كل شيء لقتلي
is you,
هل أنت،
Wu Chengwu.
وو تشينجوو.
You created me here, right?
لقد خلقتني هنا ، أليس كذلك؟
And this is where
وهذا هو المكان
you thought of every possible way to torture me.
فكرت في كل طريقة ممكنة لتعذيبي.
Stabbed me.
طعنني.
Hit me with a truck.
اضربني بشاحنة.
And you tried to kill me with your own hands.
وحاولت قتلي بيديك.
Hem.
هدب.
You seem to know me well.
يبدو أنك تعرفني جيدًا.
Then let me know you a little.
ثم دعني أعرفك قليلا.
Wu Chengwu.
وو تشينجوو.
You are so famous.
انت مشهور جدا.
Everything about you is on the internet.
كل شيء عنك موجود على الإنترنت.
You are good for nothing.
أنت جيد من أجل لا شيء.
You are trying to numb your senses with alcohol.
أنت تحاول تخدير حواسك بالكحول.
That's why you created me,
لهذا السبب خلقتني
a person who's the exact opposite of you.
شخص عكسك تمامًا.
Isn't it?
أليس كذلك؟
You gained popularity using my life.
لقد اكتسبت شعبية باستخدام حياتي.
But you didn't expect
لكنك لم تتوقع
that your wife still left you with your daughter.
أن زوجتك ما زالت تركتك مع ابنتك.
You are such a coward.
يا لك من جبان.
You couldn't even make the move to kill yourself.
لا يمكنك حتى اتخاذ هذه الخطوة لقتل نفسك.
That's why all you do is torturing me.
لهذا السبب كل ما تفعله هو تعذيبي.
Because you know I'm the only person
لأنك تعلم أنني الشخص الوحيد
that you get to have control over.
يمكنك التحكم فيها.
But,
لكن،
why did you save me?
لماذا أنقذتني
I didn't save you.
أنا لم أنقذك.
You wanted to live yourself.
كنت تريد أن تعيش بنفسك.
That day,
ذلك اليوم،
I was going to kill you.
كنت سأقتلك.
But you asked me for help.
لكنك طلبت مني المساعدة.
So I couldn't make myself do it.
لذلك لم أستطع أن أجعل نفسي أفعل ذلك.
That's where the problem is.
وهنا تكمن المشكلة.
From that day,
منذ ذلك اليوم،
you started to develop self-consciousness.
بدأت في تطوير الوعي الذاتي.
Just like now.
تماما مثل الآن.
And that's wrong.
وهذا خطأ.
You are a comic character I created.
أنت شخصية كوميدية صنعتها.
You are not a real person.
أنت لست شخص حقيقي.
And now you are trying to control me.
والآن أنت تحاول السيطرة علي.
Do you think you are the only one in pain?
هل تعتقد أنك الوحيد الذي يتألم؟
I'm in pain as well.
أنا أتألم أيضًا.
I can't sleep all night.
لا أستطيع النوم طوال الليل.
I think
أظن
I have some mental issues.
لدي بعض المشاكل العقلية.
I went to see a psychiatrist
ذهبت لرؤية طبيب نفسي
and ask my friends.
واسأل أصدقائي.
They all told me I'm joking.
قالوا لي جميعًا إنني أمزح.
I got afraid. I wanted to run away.
خفت.  كنت أريد أن أهرب.
(But I have to hold on)
(لكن لا بد لي من التمسك)
(for Yanzhu.)
(لـ Yanzhu.)
(I can make money from this to take care of her.)
(يمكنني كسب المال من هذا للاعتناء بها).
This comic still hasn't ended.
هذا الكوميدي لم ينته بعد.
It's a torture for me as well.
إنه عذاب بالنسبة لي أيضًا.
But,
لكن،
why did you suddenly come to me
لماذا أتيت إلي فجأة
and even get Yanzhu involved?
وحتى إشراك Yanzhu؟
You are a character in my comic.
أنت شخصية في فكاهي.
You are not a real person.
أنت لست شخص حقيقي.
Understand?
يفهم؟
So,
لذا،
can you tell me
هل يمكن أن تخبرني
who the murderer is?
من هو القاتل؟
There is none.
لا يوجد.
This is just a setting to make the protagonist stronger.
هذا مجرد إعداد لجعل بطل الرواية أقوى.
It's a typical trope in hero comic.
إنها مجاز نموذجي في الكوميديا ​​البطل.
I don't know
لا أعرف
who the murderer is.
من هو القاتل.
How can I believe that?
كيف يمكنني تصديق ذلك؟
That's the truth.
هذه هي الحقيقة.
When the protagonist catches the murderer,
عندما يمسك بطل الرواية بالقاتل ،
this comic will end.
سينتهي هذا الكوميدي.
So,
لذا،
do you mean that
هل تعني ذلك
my parents being murdered
والداي يقتلان
and I being mistaken as the killer
وأنا مخطئ بوصفي القاتل
are just the settings of the comic?
هي مجرد اعدادات فكاهي؟
All the pain I had to go through over the last ten years
كل الآلام التي كان عليّ أن أتحملها خلال السنوات العشر الماضية
is only a setting of the comic?
هو مجرد إعداد للكوميديا؟
You won't shoot.
لن تطلق النار.
This is your setting.
هذا هو وضعك.
I created you as a merciful person.
لقد خلقتك كشخص رحيم.
That's the way to make the readers like you.
هذه هي الطريقة لجعل القراء يحبونك.
You must be angry.
يجب أن تكون غاضبًا.
Shoot me.
اطلق النار علي.
Kill me.
اقتلني.
I've had enough anyway.
لقد كان لدي ما يكفي على أي حال.
Haha.
هاها.
What's wrong
ما هو الخطأ
with this world?
مع هذا العالم؟
Go see him.
اذهب لرؤيته.
He might live
قد يعيش
if he's lucky.
إذا كان محظوظا.
Yanzhu.
يانتشو.
I have something to say to you.
لدي ما أقوله لك.
Oh.
أوه.
How did your dad get hurt?
كيف تأذى والدك؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
It looks like a gunshot wound.
يبدو وكأنه طلق ناري.
But we didn't find the bullet.
لكننا لم نجد الرصاصة.
So we can't be sure either.
لذلك لا يمكننا التأكد أيضًا.
We are thinking
نحن نفكر
if we should call the police.
إذا كان ينبغي لنا استدعاء الشرطة.
How about this?
وماذا عن هذا؟
Tell them
اخبرهم
they can ask him after he wakes up.
يمكنهم سؤاله بعد أن يستيقظ.
Okay.
تمام.
Take care of him for now.
اعتني به الآن.
Call me anytime if there's anything.
اتصل بي في أي وقت إذا كان هناك أي شيء.
Yeah.
نعم.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Take care of him.
الاعتناء به.
Thank god. He's fine.
الحمد لله.  انه على ما يرام.
Yanzhu.
يانتشو.
What should we do now?
ماذا يجب أن نفعل الآن؟
And Jiang Zhe.
وجيانغ زهي.
How did he come to our world?
كيف أتى إلى عالمنا؟
I don't know either.
لا اعرف ايضا.
Hello, Editor.
مرحبًا أيها المحرر.
(Hello.)
(مرحبًا.)
We should have paid a visit long ago.
كان يجب أن نقوم بزيارة منذ فترة طويلة.
(The thing is,)
(الشيء هو،)
(we lose contact with Mr. Wu.)
(نفقد الاتصال بالسيد وو.)
(So we want to confirm with you)
(لذا نريد التأكيد معك)
(whether it was Mr. Wu)
(سواء كان السيد وو)
(who uploaded the latest chapter of W?)
(من قام بتحميل الفصل الأخير من W؟)
Ah?
آه؟
A new chapter?
فصل جديد؟
Okay, thank you.
حسنا شكرا لك.
The editor said
قال المحرر
there's a new chapter of W.
هناك فصل جديد من مسلسل W.
What?
ماذا؟
Look.
ينظر.
(The end)
(النهاية)
This world is from a comic.
هذا العالم من فكاهي.
And you,
وأنت،
Jiang Zhe,
جيانغ زهي ،
are the protagonist.
هي البطل.
There is none.
لا يوجد.
This is just a setting to make the protagonist stronger.
هذا مجرد إعداد لجعل بطل الرواية أقوى.
It's a typical trope in hero comic.
إنها مجاز نموذجي في الكوميديا ​​البطل.
I don't know
لا أعرف
who the murderer is.
من هو القاتل.
What's the purpose
ما هو الغرض
of all this?
من كل هذا؟
♪Looking out at you from a lighthouse far away♪
ينظر إليك من منارة بعيدة ♪
♪Cupping a few rays of sunshine♪
الحجامة بأشعة الشمس المشرقة
♪Can it♪
♪ هل يمكن ♪
♪Warm your heart?♪
♪ تدفئ قلبك؟
♪The ties between people♪
الروابط بين الناس ♪
♪Are countless and complicated♪
♪ لا تعد ولا تحصى ومعقدة ♪
♪As long as♪
♪ ما دام ♪
♪We hear♪
♪ نسمع ♪
♪Each other's heartbeats and breath♪
دقات القلب والنفس لبعضهم البعض ♪
♪I'm waiting for you to turn around♪
♪ أنا في انتظار أن تستدير ♪
♪The world is silent and I miss the hustle and bustle♪
♪ العالم صامت وافتقد الصخب والضجيج
♪Put my heart into your palm lines♪
♪ ضع قلبي في خطوط راحة يدك ♪
♪The balance of the scales of love is tipped by you♪
ميزان موازين الحب يميل إليك ♪
♪Touch your inner world♪
♪ المس عالمك الداخلي ♪
♪Start a fantasy journey♪
♪ ابدأ رحلة خيالية ♪
♪A pair of lovers have lost their minds♪
♪ زوج من العشاق فقدوا عقولهم
♪And been sinking♪
♪ وتم الغرق ♪
♪In love♪
♪ في الحب ♪
♪The ties between people♪
الروابط بين الناس ♪
♪Are countless and complicated♪
♪ لا تعد ولا تحصى ومعقدة ♪
♪As long as♪
♪ ما دام ♪
♪We hear♪
♪ نسمع ♪
♪Each other's heartbeats and breath♪
دقات القلب والنفس لبعضهم البعض ♪
♪I'm waiting for you to turn around♪
♪ أنا في انتظار أن تستدير ♪
♪The world is silent and I miss the hustle and bustle♪
♪ العالم صامت وافتقد الصخب والضجيج
♪Put my heart into your palm lines♪
♪ ضع قلبي في خطوط راحة يدك ♪
♪The balance of the scales of love is tipped by you♪
ميزان موازين الحب يميل إليك ♪
♪Touch your inner world♪
♪ المس عالمك الداخلي ♪
♪Start a fantasy journey♪
♪ ابدأ رحلة خيالية ♪
♪A pair of lovers have lost their minds♪
♪ زوج من العشاق فقدوا عقولهم
♪And been sinking♪
♪ وتم الغرق ♪
♪In love♪
♪ في الحب ♪